we are with Tania we are all with
estamos con Tania todas estamos con
Tania she is not alone I'm serious
Tania no está sola os lo digo en serio
Tania is not alone come on Tania is not
Tania no está sola vamos Tania no está
alone she is not alone Tania come on whoever has
sola no está sola Tania ánimo el que
xan planas has done what is the name of what he has
tenga xan planas ha hecho Cómo se llama
done as always supporting Loli here
hecho como siempre apoyando a Loli aquí
is has
est ha
made it have to be
hecho que tenga que se
V that a thread a thread that he has made
V que que un hilo un hilo que ha hecho
a fantastic thread about that let's say
un hilo fantástico sobre que vamos que
I have not finished reading it he
yo no me lo he terminado de leer no la
could not finish reading it because there were
ha podido terminar de leer porque era
too many letters and he could not but
demasiadas letras y ya no ha podido pero
let's say I like he made a thread
vamos que yo en plan ha hecho un hilo
defending Tania's thing no and what and
defendiendo lo de Tania no y que y
explaining that the complaint could be false
explicando que puede ser falsa la
no that it could be false no the
denuncia no que podría ser falsa no la
man's conviction the truth is no I have not finished it
hombre la verdad no no lo he terminado
yet but I have it I have it and I have a
todavía pero lo tengo lo tengo y tengo
thread a thread Dean plana yes s
que un hilo un hilo Dean plana sí s
thread says Pablo that the Joan
hilo dice Pablo que el hilo de Joan
planas thread goes on my live tomorrow nor does it
planas entra mañana en mi directo ni
quote no Pablo I do not doubt it Pablo Pablo
cotiza no Pablo no lo dudo Pablo Pablo
tomorrow we will see it is that I am not very well
mañana lo veremos es que yo no estoy muy
informed on X The truth is that no well a
puesta en X La verdad es que no pues un
thread and there you can see everything So now you can
hilo y ahí se ve todo Así que ahora se
see everything eh it has been a false complaint
ve todo eh ha sido una denuncia falsa
family it has been a false complaint okay
familia ha sido una denuncia falsa vale
eh And you're telling me that the pppa
eh Y me estáis diciendo que la pppa
answered this softer than a glove
respondió esto más suave que un guante
Neither do I but so so so soft No I
Yo tampoco la pero tan tan tan suave No
say Well I saw you very bad that day I
yo digo Bueno te vi muy mal aquel día te
saw you very bad there you ate a lot of chocolate or
vi muy mal ahí comiste mucho chocolate o
something and and you got it you ate a lot of
algo y y te entró la comiste mucho
chocolate or something and you got something the this the the you
chocolate o algo y te entró algo la esto
already know that Loli Huerta is
la la ya sabéis que Loli Huerta es
allergic to chocolate come on in case you didn't
alérgica al chocolate dala por si tú no
know okay Loli Huerta is allergic
lo sabías vale Loli Huerta es alérgica
to chocolate because in a live show she was
al chocolate porque un un directo estaba
like very red with her face very
como muy colorada con la cara muy
red and people asked her what was
colorada y la gente le preguntó que qué
wrong with her And she said that it was an allergy to
le pasaba Y dijo que era alergia al
chocolate that she had eaten a
chocolate que que se había comer un
chocolate that she was allergic to that brand
chocolate que era alérgica a esa marca
Yes yes she told me that I'm a
Sí si me ha dicho que soy alcohólica de
lifelong alcoholic, lifelong alcoholic
toda la vida yo alcohólica de toda la
while I'm with my water of
vida mientras yo estoy con mi agüita del
water served I who am not a beer drinker you
agua servi yo que no soy cervecera
know that I like Verdejo but
sabéis que a mí me gusta el verdejo pero
come on I watch Verdejo when I go out
que vamos el verdejo lo veo cuando salgo
not when I'm at home Maybe it's because I have to take
no cuando estoy en mi casa Será porque
care of my mother I have to
tengo que cuidar a mi madre tengo que
have two in front no maybe that's it I have to
tener do de frente no a lo mejor es eso
have two in front so as not to
tengo que tener do frente para no para
not make a of when I go out Then my
no hacer un de cuando sal Entonces mi
brother with my  mother
hermano con mi madre
what and I'm going to tell and I say it now
que y me vair que conte y lo digo ahora
that I'm never going to put like she has done
que nunca voy a meter como ella ha hecho
in this live to Antonio David Flores
en este directo a Antonio David flores
she has done it in this live that she
lo ha hecho ella en este directo que
is doing But what has
está haciendo Pero en qué ha metido
Antonio davil put in the only thing that I have
Antonio davil lo único que yo he
heard that Antonio davil has said is about
escuchado que ha dicho Antonio davil es
Granada
lo de granada
no send me a photo Karime but a photo
no mándame una foto Karime pero una foto
not a video a photo and
no un vídeo una foto e
the only thing that Antonio has said about
lo único que ha dicho Antonio lo de
Granada no So Loli made up that she
granada no O sea que la Loli se inventó
was in Granada that Loli says that she made up the thing
que estuvo en Granada que Loli dice que
about Granada to defend
se inventó lo de granada para defender a
Marta and Anton I don't think she
Marta y anton yo no creo que se lo
made it up to defend Marte Anton made it up to he made it up to make it seem to him
inventas para defender a Marte anton se
that he was hanging out with them it
dársela de que se juntaba con ellos me
seems to me that it's a game to this person
parece que es una jugara a esta persona
that a kiss Livi
que un beso livi
gorgeous that she
guapísima que se
deserves Javi says Dallas that you look at
merece Javi dice Dallas que mires
discord
discord
[Laughs] I'm
[Risas]
going yes it's about this scene but it's that it
voy sí es sobre la escena esta pero es
made me laugh a lot uncle
que a m me hecho mucha gracia tío
Lollyta picking up the cell phone
lollyta cogiendo el móvil
the
el
cell phone
móvil
[Laughs]
[Risas]
Air are very special don't you want to
Air son muy especiales no te quieras tú
stay with my geek that they are mine
ya quedar con mi friky que son míos
Eh  So let me not be so
Eh Así que permiti que no sea tan
bloody and not talk about that person
Sangrienta y no hable de esa persona
because good G of looking for the
porque buen G de buscarle al
chal to bite Yes or yes Even if he doesn't
chal picar Sí o sí Por más que él no se
want to get involved or ignores it, they are going to get out,
quiera meter o lo ignore lo van a sal
bite him Because if these people start
picar Porque si esta gente se empiezan a
fighting, surely Peppa is going to
pelear seguramente la la Peppa va a
prolong it Well, I know the relationship that
alargar Pues yo que sé la relación que
Loli had with Antonia viid and all
tuviera eh Loli con Antonia viid y todo
that, okay girl Oy now for Sao, no, ah,
eso vale niña Oy ahora para Sao no que
that Libi is okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, let's
ah que libi es vale vale vale vale vale
see,
vale vale vale vale vale vale vale a ver
she's like that
ella es así
but let's see about the thing with the
pero a ver lo de la lo de la le al
chocolate, can you please send it to me
chocolate me lo podéis mandar porfa
Karime or something so I can show it to
Karime o algo para para enseñárselo al
Dallas so he can
Dallas para que él
analyze it. Based on his medical experience, yes, he
analice Bajo su experiencia médica si si
believes that it is an allergy to
cree que eso es alergia al
chocolate. I have my
chocolate Yo es que tengo mi
doubts, I know. He told me that the lawyer
dudas sé A mí me dijo que el abogado
was in the house, but it happened to me that
estaba en la casa pero me pas a mí que
let's see that everything
vamos a ver que a mí todo lo que me dijo
Loli told me, I knew a long time ago, I
Loli yo me ya hace tiempo que lo supe me
believe half of it, half of it, I do
creo la mitad de la mitad su enfermedad
n't
no la
question her illness But this is that
cuestiono su enfermedad Pero esto es que
I It's that I This is  It seems like a
yo me Es que yo Esto me parece una
fantasy I don't question her illness
fantasía su enfermedad no la cuestiono
but Peppa but if you said that I was
pero Peppa pero si dijiste que te había
wrong that I had the wrong
equivocado de que te había equivocado de
word I don't question her illness I don't
palabra su enfermedad no la cuestiono No
question it there are things that mark me one a
la cuestiono hay cosas que me mar uno
troll I see that she's a troll and the troll
una trolla veo que trolla y el trolla lo
knows it I see that the troll doesn't interest me
sabe veo que el [__] ni me interesa de
where she gets her money from or where she gets it from or if she has it
dónde saca el dinero ni de dónde lo saca
if she doesn't have it I'm not interested in
ni si tiene si no tiene no me interesa
anything
nada
look I have or we have for breakfast for
mira tengo o tenemos para desayunar para
lunch for a snack and for dinner I
almorzar para merendar y para cenar
can buy some shoes when I
puedo comprarme unos zapatos cuando los
need them or I like them I can go to a
necesito o me gusta puedo ir a una boda
friend's wedding from Big Brother one not
de un amigas de gran hermano a una no a
two in recent years two I can go out to
dos en los últimos años a dos puedo ir a
eat with my friends and my friends If
comer con mis amigos y mis amigas Si en
one day I go to
cartan día me voy a los conciertos de
my children's concerts and since I'm the artist's mother the
mis hijos y como soy la mamá del artista
artist pays for it well Pepa daughter if
el artista me lo pag pues [__] hija si
you didn't need it why did you get yourself into
no te hacía falta para qué te metido en
this mess well it's because it's your
este fregado bueno es porque es tu
condition Okay but you had no
condición Vale pero no tenías ninguna
need no need to
necesidad ninguna necesidad de de
put yourself there behind Loli on the
ponerte ahí detrás de la Loli en el
side that you got yourself into because of
bando en el que te has metido por la
Loli let's see the end it's your condition without
Loli a ver fin es tu condición sin más
better but F from your face is saying No
vale pero F de tu cara está diciendo No
I
yo no tengo necesidad tengo para esto
don't have need I have for this I have for that and how should I say it I stick to it there is some information that I saw last night on Twitter from a platform colleague in this case Tania in which another
Tania en la que otro compañero de
platform colleague like
plataforma como
Mr. Oliveira and
es el señor oliveira y
lawyer that the information was taken by
abogado que la información la ha sacado
Mr. Oliveira his lawyer but not you
el señor oliveira su abogado pero no a
Javi I want a debate Loli against
tien Javi Quiero un debate Loli contra
coscu How are the
coscu Cómo están las
heads a kiss Olga I promise you that
cabezas un beso Olga os prometo ese
crossover eh if you have Ho in the chat with
crossover eh si tenéis Ho en el chat a
Francoa and Dala watching the gossip of the
francoa y a dala viendo el chisme de la
pppa and Loli I promise you that
pppa y de la Loli os prometo ese
crossover too
crossover también
C cocu with Loli I promise you
C cocu con Loli os lo prometo
eh
eh
exactly
exactamente
exactly something very private and very
exactamente algo muy privado y muy
delicate
delicado
very private eh in all the
muy privado eh en todos los medios de
media in the country on ABC in
comunicación en el país en el abc en
all eh Very private of The environment and the
todo eh Muy privado de El entorno y la
life of Tania
vida de Tania
mandarin mandarin mandarin 599 I
mandarina mandarina mandarina 599 yo te
give you for a fridge pie and so you can lick
doy para frigo pie y así puedes lamer
something delicious right a fridge pie How good
algo rico verdad un frigo pie Qué bueno
no how good eh Me  they just sent a
no qué bueno eh Me acaban de mandar un
eh I don't care I don't care about losing 5 10
eh Me da igual me da igual perder 5 10
15 20 subscribers from wherever they come from
15 20 suscriptores de donde vengan de
wherever they are
donde sean
but if there is one or some that is
pero si hay alguna o algunos que está
good what Loli is saying and what
bien lo que está diciendo Loli y lo que
Antonio intends and they are putting it right now
Antonio y lo están poniendo ahora mismo
in the
en el chat de
Loli dasas chat that if she talks about cryptocurrency
Loli dasas que si habla de criptomoneda
this It's good he put me with the you
esta Está bueno me puso con lo de los tú
no it's that of course It's that this is another
no es que claro Es que esto es otro
smells is that d it's that it's a lot of context
olores es que d es que es mucho contexto
dude you can't appear here at the end of
tío no puedes aparecer aquí al final de
the story expect us to give you all
la historia pretender que te demos todo
the context let's see This
el contexto a ver Esta
lady do you remember the pambi no doesn't it
señora tú te acuerdas del pambi no no te
sound like something pambi to you well this lady
suena de algo pambi pues esta señora
um Yes exactly what they are
em Sí exactamente lo que me están
telling me on WhatsApp not a [ __ ] year
diciendo por WhatsApp no un [__] año la
tane bothering her with a sentence a
tane dando por culo con una sentencia un
[ __ ] year bothering her and at the slightest
[__] año dando por culo y a la mínima
How she threw the video eh it has to be
Cómo ha tirado el vídeo eh tiene que
that what it shows is how it has to
estar eso lo que demuestra es comoo
be But there are more things Eh there are
tiene que estar Pero hay más cosas Eh
more things eh
hay más cosas eh
and there is
e hay
more Ah they are putting on their Twitter
más Ah que están poniendo en su Twitter
that they are preparing a very
que están preparando una demanda muy
big lawsuit Yes yes yes yes they can file all
gorda Sí sí sí si si pueden poner todas
the lawsuits that  they want yes yes you
las demandas que ellos quieran si si tú
can file all the lawsuits you
puedes poner todas las demandas que tú
want and join Yan Planas and file
quieras y y unirte a yan planas y poner
all the lawsuits you want Tania
todas las demandas que tú quieras Tania
but that sentence not That that That that
pero que esa condena no Esa esa Esa esa
jail sentence that was there that will never go
condena de cárcel que hubo ahí eso no va
away
a desaparecer nunca
okay never
vale nunca
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
that when the Pambi thing happened, Peppa
que cuando lo de pambi la Peppa
coincided with her birthday
coincidió con su fecha de cumpleaños
Dallas
Dallas
and on her
y en su
birthday she put up some number balloons
cumpleaños puso unos globos de número
that said
que ponía
10500 because she says that I took 10500 from
10500 porque dice que yo le quité 10500
the poor Pan Visito What a shame
a los pobres pan visito Que lástima
Peruvians it's that Claro you can't
peruanos es que Claro tú no puedes
appear now and that
aparecer ahora y que
exactly
exactamente
exactly V with you
exactamente V con ustedes
gentlemen my love here and love here no to
señores mi amor aquí y amor aquí no a
the atrocities look at it right now
las barbaridades mira loo ahora mismo
Wait I'm going to put a bell on it So
Espérate que le voy a poner campanilla
everyone is
Esto entonces está todo el mundo
asking me what do you think that you're going
preguntándome tú que piensas tú que esto
to talk about this you're not going to talk about it let's
lo vas a hablar no lo vas a hablar vamos
see it's not that if she doesn't have Twitter Well I do
ver no es que si no tiene Twitter Bueno
n't know if she will say it I imagine
no sé si si lo dirá me imagino
that I'm not going to comment on the subject in
que yo no voy a comentar el tema en
depth no way let's go eh I just
profundidad ni de coña vamos eh Solo
have to say something I don't know if one
tengo que decir alguna cosa no sé si una
two or three  In principle, who is the source of this
dos o tres en principio de quién viene
information? It's from someone who has
la información es de alguien que a mí me
been accusing me of,
ha estado acusando de
well, he's accusing me
e buen me está acusando
of robbing the police, of robbing
de ha robado a la policía ha robado a
min Elisa, thank you for this, eh. Thank you very much,
min Elisa gracias por este eh Muchísimas
beautiful, let
guapa
's go from equality to no, eh. He
vamos de igualdad acabado al no al no
made a video, Tinker Bell where she is his
hizo un vídeo campanilla dónde que es su
employee so that he could put it in such a
trabajadora para que lo pusiera de tal
way that it seemed that I was being with him, well,
forma que parecía que yo le estaba sea
this gentleman, I don't believe
que yo este señor yo no me creo
absolutely anything, nothing,
absolutamente nada nada
nothing, yeah, yeah, but I have to comment. I don't believe absolutely
nada ya ya pero tengo que que comentar
anything, he doesn't
son No me creo absolutamente nada no se
believe anything, Peppa, eh. No, he doesn't believe anything, eh.
cree nada Peppa eh No no se cree nada eh
Peppa,
Peppa
eh. That can't be true, eh. That until
eh eso no puede ser verdad eh eso hasta
the one from Troy confirms it, that can't
que no lo confirme al de Troya eso no
be true, eh. That ABC, El Pas and
puede ser verdad eh eso el ABC el país y
all of this have lied, but of course the
todo esto han mentido pero claro la
information that is being given is very delicate,
información que se da es muy delicada
very serious and I'm not going to get into it
muy grave y en el que yo no voy a entrar
because I have no
porque ni tengo
idea what has happened, what's happening, or
idea de lo que ha pasado de lo que pasa
what happened or
ni de lo que pasó ni de
anything, so don't ask me, are you going to take a
nada entonces no me pidáis te vas a
position? I don't take a position on anything,
posicionar yo no me posiciono con nada
I don't take a position on anything, I'll
yo no me posiciono con nada yo se lo
tell you what I've seen, what I've received  They
digo lo que he visto Lo que se me ha
have even sent me
llegado me han llegado a mandar hasta
some kind of Sentence or some
una especie de Sentencia o de una
kind of Sentence eh I don't
especie una especie de Sentencia eh No
know, a kind of Sentence but I don't
sé una especie de Sentencia pero no me
believe it then I'm not going to read it
la creo luego no la voy a leer
exactly Manuel and Martin, I don't have
exactamente Manuel y Martín yo no tengo
enough data, not even if I did I
ni datos suficiente ni aunque lo tuviera
would be able to comment on that type of
sería capaz de comentar ese tipo de
story I know that many of you, since you
historia sé que muchas de vosotras como
don't have Twitter, you don't know what
no tenéis Twitter no s no sabéis de lo
I'm talking about, you already know everything about what it's about
que hablo que ya sabréis de todo de que
But Manuel and Martin, I'm going to comment on
Pero Manuel y Martín yo voy a comentar
that, what's more, I tell you that coming from where it
eso es más os digo que viniendo de donde
comes from, she will have to provide evidence, she will have to
viene tendrá que poner pruebas tendrá
provide stories
que poner historias
because it seems to me to be a subject that is too, too, too, too
porque me parece un tema demasiado
strong so
demasiado demasiado demasiado fuerte así
up to there I imagine that Tania will
que hasta ahí yo me imagino que Tania
of course do what she has to do,
claro hará lo que tenga que
I don't know if she is going to comment on
hacer yo no sé si ella va a comentar
anything, if she is not going to comment on anything I don't know, that has been
algo si no va a comentar nada No lo sé
commented on for a long time,
eso ya se viene comentando hace tiempo
yes Tania says that she is going to prove
sí Tania dice que va que va a demostrar
things with papers, that she is going to prove
las cosas con papeles que va a demostrar
things with
las cosas con
papers, I don't know how I haven't seen her
papeles no sé cómo la no la v
through Carmen Muriel I swear to you it's that
calado Carmen Muriel Yo te juro es que
I spoke to her long before I
yo hablaba con ella antes mucho antes de
had a year and a half before having a channel I
tener un año y medio antes tener canal O
mean it wasn't because of the
sea que yo no era por el interés
economic interest, I  I can't stand these
económico yo no puedo con lo de esta
people I can't I can't stand
gente yo no
these people
puedo yo no puedo con lo de esta gente
Andy reveals have you already posted
Andy revela has puesto Ya la la
Pablo's thumbnail I mean the
miniatura de Pablo o sea está ya
live is already scheduled then
programado el directo entonces
no I mean Pablo is going to do a
no O sea Pablo mañana va a hacer un
live tomorrow Well I'll watch it to see the the Hey
directo Pues yo lo veré a ver la la Oye
Pablo be careful to see if they're going to throw it at you
Pablo ten cuidado ver si te lo van a
too eh Because
tirar también eh Porque es
these people want to talk about you a
que la esta gente quieren hablar de ti a
lot every day okay but you answering them that no no no you talk about it
tope todos los días vale pero que tú le
no
no eso ya no que tú hables de ello ya no
they about you yes eh they talk about you a lot
ellos de ti sí eh ellos de ti a tope
whatever you want nobody shuts them up
todo lo que tú quieras nadie le calla
only Loli okay but you talk about
solo Loli vale pero que tú hables de
them Ah I can't take that so well anymore
ellos Ah eso ya no lo llevo tan bien
eh then I don't know if they're going to throw this at you
eh entonces no sé si esto te lo van a
what a nerve man But how can you
tirar qué morro tío Pero cómo se puede
be so nerveless and not hold back eh
tener tan morro y no cortarse un pelo eh